{
    "subject": "resource/Fatty's_Chance_Acquaintance",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:American_films",
    "human_readable": "Fatty's Chance Acquaintance is about American films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8747365474700928,
            "question": "Is Fatty's Chance Acquaintance a documentary?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8267208933830261,
            "question": "Who directed Fatty's Chance Acquaintance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7361733913421631,
            "question": "What is the topic of Fatty's Chance Acquaintance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7258750200271606,
            "question": "What is the plot of Fatty's Chance Acquaintance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6503803133964539,
            "question": "Does Fatty's Chance Acquaintance feature famous actors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6276411414146423,
            "question": "What is the genre of Fatty's Chance Acquaintance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.621220052242279,
            "question": "What are some themes explored in Fatty's Chance Acquaintance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5671938061714172,
            "question": "Where can you watch Fatty's Chance Acquaintance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4646390974521637,
            "question": "What year was Fatty's Chance Acquaintance released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24698828160762787,
            "question": "What country are American films from?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fatty's Chance Acquaintance is about American films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7154_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Fatty's Chance Acquaintance released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7154_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you watch Fatty's Chance Acquaintance?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7154_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some themes explored in Fatty's Chance Acquaintance?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7154_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7154_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7154_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7154_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7154_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7154_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7154_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7154_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7154_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7154_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7154_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the required JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: Based on the provided context information, it appears that \"Fatty's Chance Acquaintance\" is actually a film from the Keystone Film company, directed by and starring Roscoe \"Fatty\" Arbuckle. The description does not mention American films in general, so it cannot be concluded that \"Fatty's Chance Acquaintance\" specifically deals with American films."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Fatty's Chance Acquaintance is about American films.\" The details mention it as a Keystone Film from 1915, directed by Roscoe Arbuckle and starring American actors such as Fatty Arbuckle and Billie Bennett."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The information provided does not indicate the film's subject matter is specifically about American films, but rather that one of its actors, Roscoe \"Fatty\" Arbuckle, was an American silent film actor.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}